"Kissing at High Tide"
(Remember to eat the porridge Han Zaixun)
This is
The note left by my brother
Even the handwriting
Like Jae Hoon hyung
Clean, upright and good-looking
It was the first time I learned that my brother studied architecture.
He's responsible for the great sketches
Now you are cooking me a bowl of porridge in front of me
Only then did I understand
What moves me the most
Not in business
Han Jae-hoon looks stronger than anyone else
(Remember to eat the porridge Han Zaixun)
But you think about me and care about me like this
this person
what were you doing just now
Han Zaixun
Yeah
what is this
Ah, that was a long time ago
So
Why do you still keep this?
Are you jealous?
Who said I was jealous?
I just feel a little uncomfortable
Yeah
here
only you
Only Kim Hae-joon
Let's go, little vinegar bucket
Let's go
I made this. Drink it quickly.
Drink, drink quickly
You can drink it too
You want to drink too
Ah, so hot
Thank you for your hard work
Haijun
that
Wait a minute. Sorry.
Hello mom
I have dinner with my friends
Because today is his birthday
Helped him cook mom's noodles
Didn’t you say that you can live longer by eating noodles on your birthday?
Yeah
he is my best friend
Got it
love you
Hang up
It's really touching
Don't get me wrong
It's just dust that got into my eyes
first time in my life
Someone said happy birthday to me
childhood
Every year on my birthday, my father’s secretary sends me an envelope.
There's a lot of money
But there was no such thing as "Let's have a meal together"
and my mother
mother
Died before I can remember
Like smoke, nothing is left
So I always thought
Birthdays are meant to be spent quietly like this
but you are different
You complain that cutting onions hurts your eyes
Smiling while answering my mother’s call
He even helped me make noodles by the way.
Today’s bowl of noodles
It's the first time in my life
Someone important cooked a bowl of hot noodles for me
Although the words are a bit crooked
But the smile is positive
Brother
I will wipe away your tears
I will always be by your side
So…
Don't feel uneasy
Who taught you to do this?
Isn't this a foul?
Brother
Let's eat cake
You haven't eaten a bite
what are you doing
You got cream here
©2025 SEEKMedia All Rights Reserved